wikijobs.in 2019-04-23

# Privacy Policies | Online Jobs, IT Jobs | Wisdom Jobs

* * *

Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. **is committed to respecting your online privacy and recognizes your need for suitable protection and management of any personally identifiable information (Personal Information) you share with us**

Personal Information contains any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home.For further information, you can visit **Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd.’s** web pages with without revealing any personal information about yourself.

## Technologies Used For Tracking

Some of our web pages utilize **‘cookies’** and other tracking technologies. A cookie is a small text file used to collect information about website activity. Some cookies and some other technologies may serve to remind personal information previously indicated by a web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. But please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the web site.

Tracking technologies may record information such as internet domain and host names; internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; click stream patterns; and dates and times of the accessing details of the user. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our website. We may also analyze the information that does not contain personal information for trends and statistical analysis.

## External Services

Third parties provide certain services available on www.wisdomjobs.com on behalf of Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. The provided information may contain personal information, that Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. collects on the web to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. maintains its website and mailing lists. Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect personal information on Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd.'s behalf.

Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. does not intend to transfer personal information without your consent to third parties, who are not bound to act on Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd.'s behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd.'s policy to sell personal information collected online without your consent. 

By using this website, your consent to the terms of our online privacy policy and to Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd.'s processing of personal information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. collects personal information on the web.

## Security Measures

* * *

• We ensure maximum security standards to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data of yours.

• We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

## Updating Your Information

* * *

• We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for many of our services. 

## Restricting Information Sharing And Disclosure

* * *

Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. does not lease, sell, or share personal information about you with third party (save with your consent) or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

• We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. communicate with you about offers from Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt Ltd. and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

• We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

• We consider that it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of WITS's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

• We have the right to transfer information about you incase 'WITS' is acquired or merged with another company. In this event, Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd.' will intimate you before information is transferred to the new company and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. does not lease, sell, or share personal information about you with third party (save with your consent) or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

• Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted advertisement. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the advertisement.

• Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd.' advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stockbrokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

**Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd.** works with business partners like vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers of various industries and business. For more information regarding services provides and other products please go through our detailed reference links.

## Confidentiality And Security

* * *

• We provide limited access to personal information about you to employees, who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

• We also have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet the terms with legal parameters in India to protect personal information about you. We seek to ensure compliance with the requirements of the Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules made there under to ensure the protection and preservation of your privacy policy.

## Contact Information

* * *

Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement at the contact address given on this website. If your concerns about contravention of this Privacy Policy are valid, we will employ all commercially reasonable efforts to address the same.

**Note:** The terms in this policy may be changed by Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd. at any time. 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt. Ltd.is free to offer its services to any client/prospective client without restriction.
